This is Ranma
of the Saotome School
of Anything Goes Martial Arts.
And living within the Tendo Dojo is Akane.
These two teens were arranged
to be married by their parents.
You're not the boss of me.
How annoying!
But Ranma suffers
with a small problem.
Whenever he's splashed with cold water,
he transforms into a girl.
RANMA1/2
KODACHI, THE BLACK ROSE
They gave me an extra for free.
Huh, being a girl's not so bad.
At least when I'm trying to buy food.
You must be
from Furinkan High School.
Hmm?
You silly fools.
You have less than a week to wait
until we face off.
So why are you so eager to rush?
We don't wanna hear it.
It's time to end our grudge.
We'll wipe you out, right here and now!
Hmm.
Did I miss the bandage convention?
Prepare yourself!
You won't understand. Not with words.
Since you refuse to listen...
Take this!
Hear me now? You fools!
We can stop that now.
It's pretty obvious to me you already won.
How did you see through
my ribbon technique so easily?
Tell me, girl.
You're not just any woman, are you?
Yeah, you could
definitely put it that way.
Amusing.
I won't hold back.
Women still get my full force!
I see you're much stronger
than those fools.
I'm a student going to
the St. Bacchus' School for Girls.
Kodachi the Black Rose.
You will do well to remember it.
Hmm?
- How can we live?
- It's a disaster.
Quit your whining and try to act like men.
Huh?
How could you think we're boys?
We're Furinkan's rhythmic gymnastics team.
We have a club.
I know these girls.
I think we're in the same class.
ANYTHING GOES MARTIAL ARTS
TENDO DOJO
All the rhythmic gymnastics
members are injured?
We were completely ambushed.
By none other than Kodachi the Black Rose.
I've never heard of the Black Rose.
We were less than a week away
from having a match against her.
With the way we are now,
we'll have to withdraw.
So, why me? You want me
to fill in for you or something?
We came to ask you for help
because we have no other options, Akane.
Because the theme of
the match that was happening was...
Martial Arts Rhythmic Gymnastics!
It's beautiful!
I haven't heard of that before.
Yeah, what the heck is it?
Just that!
Our school representatives are going
to face off,
- using the power of rhythmic gymnastics.
- Hmm?
ILLUSTRATION
Copy that.
Akane!
You're the only person left who stands
a chance against the Black Rose.
- Akane.
- Can't you see we're begging?
Right. I don't think I'm
quite getting it yet, but I'll do it.
I'll do whatever I can
to avenge all of you.
Thank you!
Thank you, Akane!
DOJO ENTRANCE THIS WAY
I can't believe
you took this on so quickly.
Also, can you wield these?
I'm not sure.
I've never used them before.
Even so, how hard could it be?
Is that really your plan?
Hmm?
Hey, there!
Aw, where have you been, cutie?
Come here, you.
I was getting worried about you, P-chan.
P-chan?
'Cause he's just a little piggy.
"P" as in pig, you know?
Wow.
I guess you two have gotten
pretty close, huh?
Yeah. So? Of course we are.
That's what happens
when you sleep together every night.
Every night?
Right?
But sometimes you disappear on me.
P-chan, be a good boy and stay right here.
Ranma, don't pick on him, okay?
Hmm?
So, Ryoga.
I suppose this means that
you've mentally turned into a pig too.
You clinging to Akane like that
is so pathetic.
I told you not to pick on that piggy!
Here goes nothing.
Were they supposed to drop like that, or...
You know that they weren't.
Let's try the ribbon then.
Okay!
How's this?
Uh...
Are you supposed to be
wrapped up like that?
I need you to shut up.
All right!
Is shattering the hoop
supposed to be part of it?
That's it! I hate this thing!
The worst part is I think you
might be the sorest loser I've ever seen.
I said shut it!
I will if you will.
Okay! I get it.
I suck at this.
And I'm never gonna get any better at it.
Don't act like it's my fault.
Would you like me to coach you?
- Oh?
- Hmm?
Ryoga?
What's goin' on, P-chan?
Who are you calling P-chan?
I don't know. You tell me.
Thank you, Ryoga.
You are so compassionate.
Oh, yeah?
Hmm.
Ribbon.
Incredible!
It was nothing.
You bastard.
That will be enough for today's training.
Thank you for all of your help.
The way you handled the ribbon
was quite good.
I'm sure you'll get better soon.
You mean that, Ryoga?
Sure, if you wanna believe a blatant lie.
I thought I told you to shut your mouth.
It's so much pressure.
I have less than a week to master
an entirely new form of martial arts.
Maybe this was a mistake.
I really shouldn't have agreed to help.
This is gonna be
painful to watch.
I mean, you're obviously
completely shameless.
Such a little suck-up.
Jealousy is unbecoming, you know.
Who are you calling jealous?
Hmm?
That's how it is, huh?
You just want to sneak off
and snuggle into bed with Akane.
Get back here!
So you're calling for backup.
Furinkan High's rhythmic gymnasts don't
seem to realize when they should give up.
And here I thought I taught them a lesson.
All right, Akane Tendo.
Beware the thorns of the Black Rose.
Or your blood will be the first to spill.
I'm so tired.
This regimen has been intense.
Akane Tendo.
Hmm?
The time is now!
Who are you?
I'm one of the rhythmic gymnasts
from St. Bacchus' School for Girls.
Kodachi the Black Rose.
You and I will fight next week.
I'm just here to wish you well,...
...and to ensure
we have a nice, clean fight.
You could've fooled me.
This feels way more like a sneak attack!
It was you!
You must've been the one
who ambushed those girls from my school.
So uncivilized to call it an ambush.
My philosophy in war is simple.
I must do everything within my power
to win before a match.
Yeah, but isn't this unfair?
Unfair?
A match begins long before
either of us get on the stage.
What is that supposed to mean?
I welcome you to return the blow--
Get back here!
You little...
Quit jumping around!
I told you to stop!
Hey!
- Damn it.
- Uh...
Hey! Ranma, leave P-chan alone!
Hyah!
Akane Tendo.
I see you're just as strong
as the rumors implied.
I will be coming back.
Are those rose petals?
So I'm the one that gets stuck
cleaning up your mess? For real?
Akane, are you done?
Can we stop hosting fights at night?
Need my beauty sleep.
Kodachi the Black Rose.
I'm gonna pay back all this and more
at the match.
Akane Tendo.
I'm going to crush you
long before the match ever happens.
A pig?
Wait, Ryoga!
Huh?
Are you feeling okay?
He's so handsome.
Hmm? Is this
that Kodachi Black Rose person?
- Hmm? Hmm?
- Hmm.
I... I...
I was so scared.
Hey, wait a second.
Uh, what is this?
Going to a girls' school feels
like living in monochrome without romance.
I could only practice rhythmic gymnastics.
I'd almost given up hope
of knowing the beautiful touch of a man!
I never imagined
such a sweet encounter would await me.
Uh, sir, what is your name?
I'm, uh, Ranma.
- Lord Ranma, these are for you.
- Hmm?
I took the liberty of sprinkling
some anesthetics into the bouquet.
Why would you
do something like that?
Mmm?
Listen, Lord Ranma.
You really must have more courage.
These lips are yours to take.
Go on. Steal them if you must.
Mmm...
If you're gonna do weird stuff,
don't do it over my room!
Well, what a shame
for us to get interrupted.
Lord Ranma, we'll meet again!
What the hell was the deal with her?
Hmph.
Sorry to interrupt
whatever you two were doing.
Enjoy your dreams.
I was pathetic.
Kodachi the Black Rose.
Oh, I don't ever wanna have to
lose to her.
Good morning.
No way!
Good morning, Akane.
Good morning.
Is it true? You're subbing
in the rhythmic gymnastics match?
Yep, sure am.
Awesome! Good luck with that.
It won't be a problem!
- Oh, I wanted to ask you...
- Hmm.
- Malice?
- Akane Tendo.
The time is now!
It's you again?
You got a lot of nerve jumping on me
first thing in the morning.
Jumping on you?
What an appalling accusation.
I was just coming up to say hello.
I actually came all the way here...
...because I wanted to visit Lord Ranma.
Then why did you come after me at all?
Why not go straight to Ranma!
Please wait right there for me,
Lord Ranma.
Huh? Can't stand that woman.
Hmm?
Akane.
I can already picture your gymnastics.
You're so, so elegant.
Feel the fire of my encouragement
with these red roses.
- I love you, Akane!
- Whoa!
Why are you coming after me?
Ranma Saotome.
What grudge do you still possess
against me?
You were the one who just came up
and attacked me out of nowhere--
Hmm?
Ranma, it's you.
Hmm.
Lovely.
What's that for?
I permit you to date her.
Wonderful, Lord Ranma.
I need you to calm down.
I'd never wanna date someone like you.
Hmm?
What do you feel for me? Is it hate?
No, that's not it at all. I was just, uh...
Ah, I forgot I already have
a fiancée right here.
So I'm taken.
Excuse me?
Just take the bullet for me on this one.
You really are something else.
You have a fiancée?
- You two are engaged?
- Mmm, a lover's quarrel.
- Yeah, kinda.
- ...some sort of love triangle?
How interesting.
Whoa.
What do you say to this?
We bet Lord Ranma's hand
on the result of our upcoming match.
- Huh?
- You wanna bet what?
You gotta be joking--
- It's perfectly all right, Akane.
- Hmm?
To have a clean break with Ranma,
all you need to do is lose.
What?
You won't need to throw the match
because I'll smash you
into tiny little pieces.
Lord Ranma.
Prepare yourself to be mine
the moment the match has been completed.
Good day to you.
- Black roses?
- Whoa! A petal storm!
Uh...
That woman may be no better
than a raving pervert.
But regardless, Ranma.
Do take care of my little sister.
Huh?
Back it up a bit.
Say what you just said again.
I said that you should do your best
to take care of my little sister.
It might be strange
coming from her brother.
At her core,
she is a relentless individual
with a mean twist to her personality.
Uh...
But please, Akane, refrain from
getting hurt during the match.
Once she locks on to a man,
she never lets go.
I can guarantee the fight won't be clean.
So,
that was Kuno's little sister?
They do kinda look alike
now that I'm thinking about it.
THE NIGHT BEFORE THE MATCH
Whoa.
Ha! Ha! Hyah!
Come on!
Mmm.
Hold still!
- Hyah!
- Hup. Hmm.
Quit jumping around
and let me practice on you!
Wow! You've made
a lot of progress. Nice job!
Don't patronize me.
I just wanna say, Ranma.
I hope you understand
that I'm not winning this match for you.
Well, yeah. I already knew that.
All right, then.
This isn't just about gymnastics.
There's not much point in practicing
without a partner.
Speaking of, Ryoga hasn't been around
at all for the last couple of days.
I was really counting on him.
Hmm?
P-chan!
I don't think
I've seen you around very much either.
Where have you been, huh?
You picked up momiji manju from Hiroshima
and something else from Kyoto?
Oh, P-chan. I wonder
where you were really trying to go.
I know that your sense of direction
completely sucks.
Mmm.
What about his sense of direction?
You're talking to him like he's Ryoga.
All righty, then.
Time to practice.
I already told you earlier
not to pick on him.
There we go.
Finally motivated to help me out, huh?
Okay, then. Here I go!
Hut!
There. That should do it, Akane.
Pretty clumsy, Sis. Surprised
you tripped over yourself like that.
Unfortunately, you'll have to withdraw
from the match tomorrow.
I'll still fight.
I'm not letting her win if I can help it.
Ah! Don't put too much weight on it.
Are you okay?
Ow, ow, it hurts.
Oh, no. You have to find
someone else to replace you.
You make it sound so easy.
A girl who's agile enough,
in really good shape
and is a martial arts expert
who's readily available...
Huh?
What? Hang on.
Stop looking at me like that.
I'm not getting shoved into a leotard.
We'll be up all night training.
Huh?